<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title><![CDATA[the wearther blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.wearther.cc//atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.wearther.cc/"/>
  <updated>2013-10-17T02:06:19.566Z</updated>
  <id>http://blog.wearther.cc//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ronald Suwandi]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[contact@wearther.cc]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://zespia.tw/hexo">Hexo</generator>
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deployed wearther 0.2.0]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.wearther.cc/2013/10/17/deployed-wearther-020/"/>
    <id>http://blog.wearther.cc/2013/10/17/deployed-wearther-020/</id>
    <published>2013-10-16T20:38:01.000Z</published>
    <updated>2013-10-17T02:04:15.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>New version of <a href="http://wearther.cc" target="_blank">wearther</a> (0.2.0) is now up and running with some new features including</p>
<ul>
<li>Automatic default unit detection. <em>Hooray!</em> It will use default unit based on your current location (eg. in the US Fahrenheit and MPH will be used and in Australia, Celsius and KM/H)</li>
<li>Wind speed and temperature units can be set separately. You can use Fahrenheit for temperature and KM/H for wind speed if you wish</li>
</ul>
<img src="/img/2013/10/wearther-0.2.0-settings.png" class="l-screenshot" width="300" height="300">


<ul>
<li>A Combination of arrow buttons on larger screens (ie. tablets and desktops). We received feedback that dragging the clothing combinations on larger screens was not very intuitive.</li>
</ul>
<img src="/img/2013/10/wearther-0.2.0-laptop.png" class="l-screenshot">


<ul>
<li>Options for the time duration spent outside. By default wearther takes The weighted average temperature for the next 6-12 hours (<code>Long</code> duration) before deciding what sort of clothing combinations to display. With <code>Short</code> duration now included as an alternative option, it will take the weighted average temperature for the next 2-3 hours to derive an optimal clothing combination. Perfect if you are only planning to go out for a short while</li>
<li>Reduced bandwidth usage by 50%</li>
<li>Minor UI changes (color, option back button, etc)</li>
</ul>
<p>Let us know what you think! We still have plenty of other features that need to be implemented and we are very excited about it! :D</p>
]]></content>
    <category scheme="http://blog.wearther.cc/categories/news/" term="news"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's Up!]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.wearther.cc/2013/10/14/it's-up/"/>
    <id>http://blog.wearther.cc/2013/10/14/it's-up/</id>
    <published>2013-10-14T10:46:26.000Z</published>
    <updated>2013-10-16T20:38:29.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://wearther.cc" target="_blank">wearther.cc</a> blog is now up and running! Here you will find all wearther related news, engineering and fashion tips. Stay tuned!</p>
]]></content>
    <category scheme="http://blog.wearther.cc/categories/news/" term="news"/>
  </entry>
</feed>
